[
    {
        "question": "أُوتِيَ",
        "answer": "is given",
        "pcklId": "530",
        "rootWordId": 12,
        "tlit": "ūtiya",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "7",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " فَأَمَّا مَنْ أُوتِيَ كِتَابَهُ بِيَمِينِهِ",
        "rootWord": "أ ت ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "آتَى",
        "waznEnglish": "to give",
        "waznTlit": "ātā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form IV)"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوتِيَ",
        "answer": "is given",
        "pcklId": "531",
        "rootWordId": 12,
        "tlit": "ūtiya",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "10",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " وَأَمَّا مَنْ أُوتِيَ كِتَابَهُ وَرَاءَ ظَهْرِهِ",
        "rootWord": "أ ت ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "آتَى",
        "waznEnglish": "to give",
        "waznTlit": "ātā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form IV)"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a reward",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "rootWordId": 18,
        "tlit": "ajrun",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "25",
        "wordnum": "7",
        "arabicAyah": " إِلَّا الَّذِينَ آمَنُوا وَعَمِلُوا الصَّالِحَاتِ لَهُمْ أَجْرٌ غَيْرُ مَمْنُونٍ",
        "rootWord": "أ ج ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَجْر",
        "waznEnglish": "reward, payment, dowry",
        "waznTlit": "ajr",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "When",
        "pcklId": "383",
        "rootWordId": 27,
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "1",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " إِذَا السَّمَاءُ انْشَقَّتْ",
        "rootWord": "إِذَا",
        "rootWordType": "nominal",
        "wazn": "إِذَا",
        "waznEnglish": "when",
        "waznTlit": "idhā",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Time adverb)"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "384",
        "rootWordId": 27,
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "3",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا الْأَرْضُ مُدَّتْ",
        "rootWord": "إِذَا",
        "rootWordType": "nominal",
        "wazn": "إِذَا",
        "waznEnglish": "when",
        "waznTlit": "idhā",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Time adverb)"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "385",
        "rootWordId": 27,
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "18",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " وَالْقَمَرِ إِذَا اتَّسَقَ",
        "rootWord": "إِذَا",
        "rootWordType": "nominal",
        "wazn": "إِذَا",
        "waznEnglish": "when",
        "waznTlit": "idhā",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Time adverb)"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "386",
        "rootWordId": 27,
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "21",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا قُرِئَ عَلَيْهِمُ الْقُرْآنُ لَا يَسْجُدُونَ",
        "rootWord": "إِذَا",
        "rootWordType": "nominal",
        "wazn": "إِذَا",
        "waznEnglish": "when",
        "waznTlit": "idhā",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Time adverb)"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَذِنَتْ",
        "answer": "And has listened",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "rootWordId": 29,
        "tlit": "wa-adhinat",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "2",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " وَأَذِنَتْ لِرَبِّهَا وَحُقَّتْ",
        "rootWord": "أ ذ ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَذِنَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to permit",
        "waznTlit": "adhina",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَذِنَتْ",
        "answer": "And has listened",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "rootWordId": 29,
        "tlit": "wa-adhinat",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "5",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " وَأَذِنَتْ لِرَبِّهَا وَحُقَّتْ",
        "rootWord": "أ ذ ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَذِنَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to permit",
        "waznTlit": "adhina",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضُ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "453",
        "rootWordId": 32,
        "tlit": "l-arḍu",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "3",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا الْأَرْضُ مُدَّتْ",
        "rootWord": "أ ر ض",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أ ر ض",
        "waznEnglish": "the Earth, land",
        "waznTlit": "hamza rā ḍād",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "Except",
        "pcklId": "653",
        "rootWordId": 58,
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "25",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " إِلَّا الَّذِينَ آمَنُوا وَعَمِلُوا الصَّالِحَاتِ لَهُمْ أَجْرٌ غَيْرُ مَمْنُونٍ",
        "rootWord": "إِلَّا",
        "rootWordType": "particle",
        "wazn": "إِلَّا",
        "waznEnglish": "except",
        "waznTlit": "illā",
        "waznType": "Particle (Exceptive particle)"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "Those who",
        "pcklId": "1407",
        "rootWordId": 59,
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "22",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " بَلِ الَّذِينَ كَفَرُوا يُكَذِّبُونَ",
        "rootWord": "ٱلَّذِى",
        "rootWordType": "nominal",
        "wazn": "ٱلَّذِى",
        "waznEnglish": "who, which, that",
        "waznTlit": "alladhī",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Relative pronoun)"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1408",
        "rootWordId": 59,
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "25",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " إِلَّا الَّذِينَ آمَنُوا وَعَمِلُوا الصَّالِحَاتِ لَهُمْ أَجْرٌ غَيْرُ مَمْنُونٍ",
        "rootWord": "ٱلَّذِى",
        "rootWordType": "nominal",
        "wazn": "ٱلَّذِى",
        "waznEnglish": "who, which, that",
        "waznTlit": "alladhī",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Relative pronoun)"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلِيمٍ",
        "answer": "painful",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "rootWordId": 60,
        "tlit": "alīmin",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "24",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " فَبَشِّرْهُمْ بِعَذَابٍ أَلِيمٍ",
        "rootWord": "أ ل م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَلِيم",
        "waznEnglish": "painful",
        "waznTlit": "alīm",
        "waznType": "Adjective"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "2828",
        "rootWordId": 61,
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "23",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " وَاللَّهُ أَعْلَمُ بِمَا يُوعُونَ",
        "rootWord": "أ ل ه",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ٱللَّه",
        "waznEnglish": "Allah",
        "waznTlit": "allah",
        "waznType": "Proper noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "732",
        "rootWordId": 63,
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "6",
        "wordnum": "5",
        "arabicAyah": " يَا أَيُّهَا الْإِنْسَانُ إِنَّكَ كَادِحٌ إِلَىٰ رَبِّكَ",
        "rootWord": "إِلَىٰ",
        "rootWordType": "preposition",
        "wazn": "إِلَىٰ",
        "waznEnglish": "to, toward, until",
        "waznTlit": "ilā",
        "waznType": "Preposition"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "733",
        "rootWordId": 63,
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "9",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " وَيَنْقَلِبُ إِلَىٰ أَهْلِهِ مَسْرُورًا",
        "rootWord": "إِلَىٰ",
        "rootWordType": "preposition",
        "wazn": "إِلَىٰ",
        "waznEnglish": "to, toward, until",
        "waznTlit": "ilā",
        "waznType": "Preposition"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَمَّا",
        "answer": "Then as for",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "rootWordId": 73,
        "tlit": "fa-ammā",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "7",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " فَأَمَّا مَنْ أُوتِيَ كِتَابَهُ بِيَمِينِهِ",
        "rootWord": "أَمَّا",
        "rootWordType": "particle",
        "wazn": "أَمَّا",
        "waznEnglish": "Then as for",
        "waznTlit": "ammā",
        "waznType": "Particle (Explanation particle)"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَمَّا",
        "answer": "But as for",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "rootWordId": 73,
        "tlit": "wa-ammā",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "10",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " وَأَمَّا مَنْ أُوتِيَ كِتَابَهُ وَرَاءَ ظَهْرِهِ",
        "rootWord": "أَمَّا",
        "rootWordType": "particle",
        "wazn": "أَمَّا",
        "waznEnglish": "Then as for",
        "waznTlit": "ammā",
        "waznType": "Particle (Explanation particle)"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "they believe",
        "pcklId": "548",
        "rootWordId": 75,
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "20",
        "wordnum": "4",
        "arabicAyah": " فَمَا لَهُمْ لَا يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "rootWord": "أ م ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ءَامَنَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to believe",
        "waznTlit": "āmana",
        "waznType": "Verb (form IV)"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "549",
        "rootWordId": 75,
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "25",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " إِلَّا الَّذِينَ آمَنُوا وَعَمِلُوا الصَّالِحَاتِ لَهُمْ أَجْرٌ غَيْرُ مَمْنُونٍ",
        "rootWord": "أ م ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ءَامَنَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to believe",
        "waznTlit": "āmana",
        "waznType": "Verb (form IV)"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسَانُ",
        "answer": "mankind",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "rootWordId": 78,
        "tlit": "l-insānu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "6",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " يَا أَيُّهَا الْإِنْسَانُ إِنَّكَ كَادِحٌ إِلَىٰ رَبِّكَ كَدْحًا",
        "rootWord": "أ ن س",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "إِنسَٰن",
        "waznEnglish": "you perceive",
        "waznTlit": "insān",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلِهِ",
        "answer": "his people",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "rootWordId": 82,
        "tlit": "ahlihi",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "9",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " وَيَنْقَلِبُ إِلَىٰ أَهْلِهِ مَسْرُورًا",
        "rootWord": "أ ه ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أ ه ل",
        "waznEnglish": "(the) People",
        "waznTlit": "hamza hā lām",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلِهِ",
        "answer": "his people",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "rootWordId": 82,
        "tlit": "ahlihi",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "13",
        "wordnum": "4",
        "arabicAyah": " إِنَّهُ كَانَ فِي أَهْلِهِ مَسْرُورًا",
        "rootWord": "أ ه ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أ ه ل",
        "waznEnglish": "(the) People",
        "waznTlit": "hamza hā lām",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَبَشِّرْهُمْ",
        "answer": "so give them tidings",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "rootWordId": 128,
        "tlit": "fabashir'hum",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "24",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " فَبَشِّرْهُمْ بِعَذَابٍ أَلِيمٍ",
        "rootWord": "ب ش ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "بُشِّرَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to give glad tidings",
        "waznTlit": "bushira",
        "waznType": "Verb (form II)"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَصِيرًا",
        "answer": "All-Seer",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "rootWordId": 129,
        "tlit": "baṣīran",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "15",
        "wordnum": "6",
        "arabicAyah": " بَلَىٰ إِنَّ رَبَّهُ كَانَ بِهِ بَصِيرًا",
        "rootWord": "ب ص ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "بَصِير",
        "waznEnglish": "I perceived",
        "waznTlit": "baṣīr",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Noun)"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثُبُورًا",
        "answer": "(for) destruction",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "rootWordId": 195,
        "tlit": "thubūran",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "11",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " فَسَوْفَ يَدْعُو ثُبُورًا",
        "rootWord": "ث ب ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ثُبُور",
        "waznEnglish": "(for) destruction",
        "waznTlit": "thubūr",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحَاسَبُ",
        "answer": "his account will be taken",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "rootWordId": 316,
        "tlit": "yuḥāsabu",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "8",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " فَسَوْفَ يُحَاسَبُ حِسَابًا يَسِيرًا",
        "rootWord": "ح س ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "حَاسَبْ",
        "waznEnglish": "to take to account",
        "waznTlit": "ḥāsab",
        "waznType": "Verb (form III)"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِسَابًا",
        "answer": "an account",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "rootWordId": 316,
        "tlit": "ḥisāban",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "8",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " فَسَوْفَ يُحَاسَبُ حِسَابًا يَسِيرًا",
        "rootWord": "ح س ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "حِسَاب",
        "waznEnglish": "(do) you think",
        "waznTlit": "ḥisāb",
        "waznType": "Verbal noun (form III) (Noun)"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَحُقَّتْ",
        "answer": "and was obligated",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "rootWordId": 344,
        "tlit": "waḥuqqat",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "2",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " وَأَذِنَتْ لِرَبِّهَا وَحُقَّتْ",
        "rootWord": "ح ق ق",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "حَقَّ",
        "waznEnglish": "to justify, to prove true",
        "waznTlit": "ḥaqqa",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَحُقَّتْ",
        "answer": "and was obligated",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "rootWordId": 344,
        "tlit": "waḥuqqat",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "5",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " وَأَذِنَتْ لِرَبِّهَا وَحُقَّتْ",
        "rootWord": "ح ق ق",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "حَقَّ",
        "waznEnglish": "to justify, to prove true",
        "waznTlit": "ḥaqqa",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحُورَ",
        "answer": "he would return",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 367,
        "tlit": "yaḥūra",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "14",
        "wordnum": "5",
        "arabicAyah": " إِنَّهُ ظَنَّ أَنْ لَنْ يَحُورَ",
        "rootWord": "ح و ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "يَحُورَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to return",
        "waznTlit": "yaḥūra",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَخَلَّتْ",
        "answer": "and becomes empty",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "rootWordId": 433,
        "tlit": "watakhallat",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "4",
        "wordnum": "4",
        "arabicAyah": " وَأَلْقَتْ مَا فِيهَا وَتَخَلَّتْ",
        "rootWord": "خ ل و",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "تَخَلَّتْ",
        "waznEnglish": "to become empty",
        "waznTlit": "takhallat",
        "waznType": "Verb (form V)"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدْعُو",
        "answer": "he will call",
        "pcklId": "167",
        "rootWordId": 474,
        "tlit": "yadʿū",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "11",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " فَسَوْفَ يَدْعُو ثُبُورًا",
        "rootWord": "د ع و",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "دَعَا",
        "waznEnglish": "to call, to invite, to pray",
        "waznTlit": "daʿā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِرَبِّهَا",
        "answer": "to its Lord",
        "pcklId": "939",
        "rootWordId": 524,
        "tlit": "lirabbihā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "2",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " وَأَذِنَتْ لِرَبِّهَا وَحُقَّتْ",
        "rootWord": "ر ب ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "رَبّ",
        "waznEnglish": "the Lord",
        "waznTlit": "rabb",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِرَبِّهَا",
        "answer": "to its Lord",
        "pcklId": "940",
        "rootWordId": 524,
        "tlit": "lirabbihā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "5",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " وَأَذِنَتْ لِرَبِّهَا وَحُقَّتْ",
        "rootWord": "ر ب ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "رَبّ",
        "waznEnglish": "the Lord",
        "waznTlit": "rabb",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "941",
        "rootWordId": 524,
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "6",
        "wordnum": "6",
        "arabicAyah": " يَا أَيُّهَا الْإِنْسَانُ إِنَّكَ كَادِحٌ إِلَىٰ رَبِّكَ كَدْحًا فَمُلَاقِيهِ",
        "rootWord": "ر ب ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "رَبّ",
        "waznEnglish": "the Lord",
        "waznTlit": "rabb",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّهُ",
        "answer": "his Lord",
        "pcklId": "942",
        "rootWordId": 524,
        "tlit": "rabbahu",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "15",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " بَلَىٰ إِنَّ رَبَّهُ كَانَ بِهِ بَصِيرًا",
        "rootWord": "ر ب ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "رَبّ",
        "waznEnglish": "the Lord",
        "waznTlit": "rabb",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَتَرْكَبُنَّ",
        "answer": "You will surely embark",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "rootWordId": 580,
        "tlit": "latarkabunna",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "19",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " لَتَرْكَبُنَّ طَبَقًا عَنْ طَبَقٍ",
        "rootWord": "ر ك ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "رَكِبَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to ride, to embark",
        "waznTlit": "rakiba",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْجُدُونَ",
        "answer": "they prostrate",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "rootWordId": 659,
        "tlit": "yasjudūna",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "21",
        "wordnum": "6",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا قُرِئَ عَلَيْهِمُ الْقُرْآنُ لَا يَسْجُدُونَ",
        "rootWord": "س ج د",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "سَجَدَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to prostrate",
        "waznTlit": "sajada",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسْرُورًا",
        "answer": "happily",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "rootWordId": 681,
        "tlit": "masrūran",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "9",
        "wordnum": "4",
        "arabicAyah": " وَيَنْقَلِبُ إِلَىٰ أَهْلِهِ مَسْرُورًا",
        "rootWord": "س ر ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "مَسْرُور",
        "waznEnglish": "pleasing",
        "waznTlit": "masrūr",
        "waznType": "Passive participle"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسْرُورًا",
        "answer": "happy",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "rootWordId": 681,
        "tlit": "masrūran",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "13",
        "wordnum": "5",
        "arabicAyah": " إِنَّهُ كَانَ فِي أَهْلِهِ مَسْرُورًا",
        "rootWord": "س ر ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "مَسْرُور",
        "waznEnglish": "pleasing",
        "waznTlit": "masrūr",
        "waznType": "Passive participle"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَعِيرًا",
        "answer": "(in) a Blaze",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "rootWordId": 691,
        "tlit": "saʿīran",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "12",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " وَيَصْلَىٰ سَعِيرًا",
        "rootWord": "س ع ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "سَعِير",
        "waznEnglish": "is set ablaze",
        "waznTlit": "saʿīr",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءُ",
        "answer": "the sky",
        "pcklId": "350",
        "rootWordId": 726,
        "tlit": "l-samāu",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "1",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " إِذَا السَّمَاءُ انْشَقَّتْ",
        "rootWord": "س م و",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "سَمَآء",
        "waznEnglish": "[I] (have) named her",
        "waznTlit": "samā",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالشَّفَقِ",
        "answer": "by the twilight glow",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "rootWordId": 783,
        "tlit": "bil-shafaqi",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "16",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " فَلَا أُقْسِمُ بِالشَّفَقِ",
        "rootWord": "ش ف ق",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "شَّفَق",
        "waznEnglish": "and they feared",
        "waznTlit": "shafaq",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "انْشَقَّتْ",
        "answer": "is split asunder",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "rootWordId": 787,
        "tlit": "inshaqqat",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "1",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " إِذَا السَّمَاءُ انْشَقَّتْ",
        "rootWord": "ش ق ق",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ٱنشَقَّ",
        "waznEnglish": "to split",
        "waznTlit": "inshaqqa",
        "waznType": "Verb (form VII)"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحَاتِ",
        "answer": "righteous deeds",
        "pcklId": "163",
        "rootWordId": 854,
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥāti",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "25",
        "wordnum": "5",
        "arabicAyah": " إِلَّا الَّذِينَ آمَنُوا وَعَمِلُوا الصَّالِحَاتِ لَهُمْ أَجْرٌ غَيْرُ مَمْنُونٍ",
        "rootWord": "ص ل ح",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "صَّٰلِحَٰت",
        "waznEnglish": "(were) righteous",
        "waznTlit": "ṣāliḥāt",
        "waznType": "Active participle"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَصْلَىٰ",
        "answer": "And he will burn",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "rootWordId": 858,
        "tlit": "wayaṣlā",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "12",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " وَيَصْلَىٰ سَعِيرًا",
        "rootWord": "ص ل ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "يَصْلَى",
        "waznEnglish": "to burn",
        "waznTlit": "yaṣlā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَبَقًا",
        "answer": "(to) stage",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "rootWordId": 904,
        "tlit": "ṭabaqan",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "19",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " لَتَرْكَبُنَّ طَبَقًا عَنْ طَبَقٍ",
        "rootWord": "ط ب ق",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ط ب ق",
        "waznEnglish": "one above another",
        "waznTlit": "ṭā bā qāf",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Noun)"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَبَقٍ",
        "answer": "stage",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "rootWordId": 904,
        "tlit": "ṭabaqin",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "19",
        "wordnum": "4",
        "arabicAyah": " لَتَرْكَبُنَّ طَبَقًا عَنْ طَبَقٍ",
        "rootWord": "ط ب ق",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ط ب ق",
        "waznEnglish": "one above another",
        "waznTlit": "ṭā bā qāf",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Noun)"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَنَّ",
        "answer": "(had) thought",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "rootWordId": 944,
        "tlit": "ẓanna",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "14",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " إِنَّهُ ظَنَّ أَنْ لَنْ يَحُورَ",
        "rootWord": "ظ ن ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ظَنَّ",
        "waznEnglish": "to think, to assume, to guess",
        "waznTlit": "ẓanna",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَهْرِهِ",
        "answer": "his back",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "rootWordId": 945,
        "tlit": "ẓahrihi",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "10",
        "wordnum": "6",
        "arabicAyah": " وَأَمَّا مَنْ أُوتِيَ كِتَابَهُ وَرَاءَ ظَهْرِهِ",
        "rootWord": "ظ ه ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ظَهْر",
        "waznEnglish": "(is) apparent",
        "waznTlit": "ẓahr",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِعَذَابٍ",
        "answer": "of a punishment",
        "pcklId": "357",
        "rootWordId": 968,
        "tlit": "biʿadhābin",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "24",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " فَبَشِّرْهُمْ بِعَذَابٍ أَلِيمٍ",
        "rootWord": "ع ذ ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عَذَاب",
        "waznEnglish": "and He will punish",
        "waznTlit": "ʿadhāb",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "(is) most knowing",
        "pcklId": "459",
        "rootWordId": 1016,
        "tlit": "aʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "23",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " وَاللَّهُ أَعْلَمُ بِمَا يُوعُونَ",
        "rootWord": "ع ل م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَعْلَم",
        "waznEnglish": "they know",
        "waznTlit": "aʿlam",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Noun)"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَمِلُوا",
        "answer": "and do",
        "pcklId": "269",
        "rootWordId": 1022,
        "tlit": "waʿamilū",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "25",
        "wordnum": "4",
        "arabicAyah": " إِلَّا الَّذِينَ آمَنُوا وَعَمِلُوا الصَّالِحَاتِ لَهُمْ أَجْرٌ غَيْرُ مَمْنُونٍ",
        "rootWord": "ع م ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عَمِلَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to do, to work",
        "waznTlit": "ʿamila",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْرُ",
        "answer": "never",
        "pcklId": "151",
        "rootWordId": 1095,
        "tlit": "ghayru",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "25",
        "wordnum": "8",
        "arabicAyah": " إِلَّا الَّذِينَ آمَنُوا وَعَمِلُوا الصَّالِحَاتِ لَهُمْ أَجْرٌ غَيْرُ مَمْنُونٍ",
        "rootWord": "غ ي ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "غَيْر",
        "waznEnglish": "so they will surely change",
        "waznTlit": "ghayr",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Adjective)"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُرِئَ",
        "answer": "is recited",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "rootWordId": 1186,
        "tlit": "quri-a",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "21",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا قُرِئَ عَلَيْهِمُ الْقُرْآنُ لَا يَسْجُدُونَ",
        "rootWord": "ق ر أ",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "قَرَأَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to read, to recite",
        "waznTlit": "qara-a",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرْآنُ",
        "answer": "the Quran",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "rootWordId": 1186,
        "tlit": "l-qur'ānu",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "21",
        "wordnum": "4",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا قُرِئَ عَلَيْهِمُ الْقُرْآنُ لَا يَسْجُدُونَ",
        "rootWord": "ق ر أ",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "قُرْءَان",
        "waznEnglish": "is recited",
        "waznTlit": "qur'ān",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Proper noun)"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُقْسِمُ",
        "answer": "I swear",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "rootWordId": 1201,
        "tlit": "uq'simu",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "16",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " فَلَا أُقْسِمُ بِالشَّفَقِ",
        "rootWord": "ق س م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَقْسَمُ",
        "waznEnglish": "to swear",
        "waznTlit": "aqsamu",
        "waznType": "Verb (form IV)"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَنْقَلِبُ",
        "answer": "And he will return",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "rootWordId": 1222,
        "tlit": "wayanqalibu",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "9",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " وَيَنْقَلِبُ إِلَىٰ أَهْلِهِ مَسْرُورًا",
        "rootWord": "ق ل ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ٱنقَلَبَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to turn back, to return",
        "waznTlit": "inqalaba",
        "waznType": "Verb (form VII)"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْقَمَرِ",
        "answer": "And the moon",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "rootWordId": 1229,
        "tlit": "wal-qamari",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "18",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " وَالْقَمَرِ إِذَا اتَّسَقَ",
        "rootWord": "ق م ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ق م ر",
        "waznEnglish": "the moon",
        "waznTlit": "qāf mīm rā",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابَهُ",
        "answer": "his record",
        "pcklId": "305",
        "rootWordId": 1256,
        "tlit": "kitābahu",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "7",
        "wordnum": "4",
        "arabicAyah": " فَأَمَّا مَنْ أُوتِيَ كِتَابَهُ بِيَمِينِهِ",
        "rootWord": "ك ت ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "كِتَٰب",
        "waznEnglish": "write",
        "waznTlit": "kitāb",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابَهُ",
        "answer": "his record",
        "pcklId": "306",
        "rootWordId": 1256,
        "tlit": "kitābahu",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "10",
        "wordnum": "4",
        "arabicAyah": " وَأَمَّا مَنْ أُوتِيَ كِتَابَهُ وَرَاءَ ظَهْرِهِ",
        "rootWord": "ك ت ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "كِتَٰب",
        "waznEnglish": "write",
        "waznTlit": "kitāb",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَدْحًا",
        "answer": "(with) exertion",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 1260,
        "tlit": "kadḥan",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "6",
        "wordnum": "7",
        "arabicAyah": " يَا أَيُّهَا الْإِنْسَانُ إِنَّكَ كَادِحٌ إِلَىٰ رَبِّكَ كَدْحًا فَمُلَاقِيهِ",
        "rootWord": "ك د ح",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "كَدْح",
        "waznEnglish": "(with) exertion",
        "waznTlit": "kadḥ",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَادِحٌ",
        "answer": "(are) laboring",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "rootWordId": 1260,
        "tlit": "kādiḥun",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "6",
        "wordnum": "4",
        "arabicAyah": " يَا أَيُّهَا الْإِنْسَانُ إِنَّكَ كَادِحٌ إِلَىٰ رَبِّكَ",
        "rootWord": "ك د ح",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "كَادِح",
        "waznEnglish": "(with) exertion",
        "waznTlit": "kādiḥ",
        "waznType": "Active participle"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُكَذِّبُونَ",
        "answer": "deny",
        "pcklId": "179",
        "rootWordId": 1263,
        "tlit": "yukadhibūna",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "22",
        "wordnum": "4",
        "arabicAyah": " بَلِ الَّذِينَ كَفَرُوا يُكَذِّبُونَ",
        "rootWord": "ك ذ ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "كَذَّبَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to deny, to reject",
        "waznTlit": "kadhaba",
        "waznType": "Verb (form II)"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "283",
        "rootWordId": 1280,
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "22",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " بَلِ الَّذِينَ كَفَرُوا يُكَذِّبُونَ",
        "rootWord": "ك ف ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "كَفَرَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to disbelieve",
        "waznTlit": "kafara",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "had been",
        "pcklId": "1349",
        "rootWordId": 1305,
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "13",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " إِنَّهُ كَانَ فِي أَهْلِهِ مَسْرُورًا",
        "rootWord": "ك و ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "كَانَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to be",
        "waznTlit": "kāna",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "was",
        "pcklId": "1350",
        "rootWordId": 1305,
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "15",
        "wordnum": "4",
        "arabicAyah": " بَلَىٰ إِنَّ رَبَّهُ كَانَ بِهِ بَصِيرًا",
        "rootWord": "ك و ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "كَانَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to be",
        "waznTlit": "kāna",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَلْقَتْ",
        "answer": "And has cast out",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "rootWordId": 1347,
        "tlit": "wa-alqat",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "4",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " وَأَلْقَتْ مَا فِيهَا وَتَخَلَّتْ",
        "rootWord": "ل ق ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَلْقَىٰٓ",
        "waznEnglish": "to cast, to throw, to meet, to offer",
        "waznTlit": "alqā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form IV)"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَمُلَاقِيهِ",
        "answer": "and you (will) meet Him",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "rootWordId": 1347,
        "tlit": "famulāqīhi",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "6",
        "wordnum": "8",
        "arabicAyah": " يَا أَيُّهَا الْإِنْسَانُ إِنَّكَ كَادِحٌ إِلَىٰ رَبِّكَ كَدْحًا فَمُلَاقِيهِ",
        "rootWord": "ل ق ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "مُلَٰقِي",
        "waznEnglish": "they meet",
        "waznTlit": "mulāqī",
        "waznType": "Active participle (form III)"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّيْلِ",
        "answer": "And the night",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "rootWordId": 1364,
        "tlit": "wa-al-layli",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "17",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " وَاللَّيْلِ وَمَا وَسَقَ",
        "rootWord": "ل ي ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "لَيْل",
        "waznEnglish": "of the night",
        "waznTlit": "layl",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Noun)"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُدَّتْ",
        "answer": "is spread",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "rootWordId": 1379,
        "tlit": "muddat",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "3",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " وَإِذَا الْأَرْضُ مُدَّتْ",
        "rootWord": "م د د",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "مَدَّ",
        "waznEnglish": "to spread, to extend, to prolong",
        "waznTlit": "madda",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَمْنُونٍ",
        "answer": "ending",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "rootWordId": 1419,
        "tlit": "mamnūnin",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "25",
        "wordnum": "9",
        "arabicAyah": " إِلَّا الَّذِينَ آمَنُوا وَعَمِلُوا الصَّالِحَاتِ لَهُمْ أَجْرٌ غَيْرُ مَمْنُونٍ",
        "rootWord": "م ن ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "مَمْنُون",
        "waznEnglish": "bestowed a Favor",
        "waznTlit": "mamnūn",
        "waznType": "Passive participle"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَاءَ",
        "answer": "behind",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "rootWordId": 1604,
        "tlit": "warāa",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "10",
        "wordnum": "5",
        "arabicAyah": " وَأَمَّا مَنْ أُوتِيَ كِتَابَهُ وَرَاءَ ظَهْرِهِ",
        "rootWord": "و ر ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "وَرَآء",
        "waznEnglish": "to hide",
        "waznTlit": "warā",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Location adverb)"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَسَقَ",
        "answer": "it envelops",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 1610,
        "tlit": "wasaqa",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "17",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " وَاللَّيْلِ وَمَا وَسَقَ",
        "rootWord": "و س ق",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "وَسَقَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to envelops",
        "waznTlit": "wasaqa",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّسَقَ",
        "answer": "it becomes full",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "rootWordId": 1610,
        "tlit": "ittasaqa",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "18",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " وَالْقَمَرِ إِذَا اتَّسَقَ",
        "rootWord": "و س ق",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ٱتَّسَقَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to be full",
        "waznTlit": "ittasaqa",
        "waznType": "Verb (form VIII)"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُوعُونَ",
        "answer": "they keep within themselves",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "rootWordId": 1628,
        "tlit": "yūʿūna",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "23",
        "wordnum": "4",
        "arabicAyah": " وَاللَّهُ أَعْلَمُ بِمَا يُوعُونَ",
        "rootWord": "و ع ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَوْعَىٰٓ",
        "waznEnglish": "to hoard, to keep",
        "waznTlit": "awʿā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form IV)"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسِيرًا",
        "answer": "easy",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "rootWordId": 1658,
        "tlit": "yasīran",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "8",
        "wordnum": "4",
        "arabicAyah": " فَسَوْفَ يُحَاسَبُ حِسَابًا يَسِيرًا",
        "rootWord": "ي س ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "يَسِير",
        "waznEnglish": "We (have) made it easy",
        "waznTlit": "yasīr",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Adjective)"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِيَمِينِهِ",
        "answer": "in his right (hand)",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "rootWordId": 1662,
        "tlit": "biyamīnihi",
        "frequency": "71",
        "surahnum": "84",
        "ayahnum": "7",
        "wordnum": "5",
        "arabicAyah": " فَأَمَّا مَنْ أُوتِيَ كِتَابَهُ بِيَمِينِهِ",
        "rootWord": "ي م ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "يَمِين",
        "waznEnglish": "the right",
        "waznTlit": "yamīn",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    }
]